 


  let allQs = [
    
    
    {
        "Question":"Which is largest state in United States?",
        "Answer":"Arizona",
        "Options":"Texas,Arizona,California,Indiana"
    },
    
    {
        "Question":"What is tallest waterfall in the world?",
        "Answer":"Angel falls",
        "Options":"niagara falls,Iguazu alls,Victoria falls,Angel falls",
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is tallest mountains in United States",
        "Answer":"Mount Mckinley",
        "Options":"Mount Mckinley,Mount Kilimanjaro,Himalayas,Kangchenjunga",
    },
    
    {
        "Question":"What is the world's biggest river, by volume of water discharged? United States",
        "Answer":"Amazon",
        "Options":"Texas,Arizona,California,Amazon"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What  is the smallest country",
        "Answer":"Vatican City",
        "Options":"Australia,germany,Vatican City,United states"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What was the biggest land empire of all time",
        "Answer":"Mongol Empire",
        "Options":"Mongol Empire,Russia Empire,Spanish Empire,Birtish Empire"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What country has the largest Muslim population",
        "Answer":"Indonesia",
        "Options":"India,Pakistan,Indonesia,Bangladesh"
    },
    
    {
        "Question":"What is largest population in the world",
        "Answer":"India",
        "Options":"Chiana,India,Pakistan,united state"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the capital of the Pakistan",
        "Answer":"Islamabad",
        "Options":"Islamabad,Punjab,Sindh,Balochistan"
    },
    
    {
        "Question":"What is the nickname of Paris",
        "Answer":"City of light",
        "Options":"City of blue light,City of light,Star light,bright"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the oldest University in England",
        "Answer":"Oxfond",
        "Options":"Washington,Arizona,California,Oxfond"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the world's first national park",
        "Answer":"Yellowstone national park",
        "Options":"Yellowstone national park,Jasper national,Yosemite national,Olympic national"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which one of the original 13 colonies doesn't border the Atlantic Ocean",
        "Answer":"Pennsylvania",
        "Options":"Pennsylvania,Arizona,California,Indiana"
    },
    
    {
        "Question":"Which continent is the United States located in",
        "Answer":"North America",
        "Options":"North America,South America,Africa,Europe"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which Ocean border the United States on the east",
        "Answer":"Atlantic",
        "Options":"Atlantic,Arizona,California,Indiana"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What country is our neighbor to the north",
        "Answer":"Canada",
        "Options":"Russia,Canada,Mexico,Newzland"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What country is our neighbor to the south",
        "Answer":"Mexico",
        "Options":"Texas,Arizona,Mexico,Indiana"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What state does the Mississippi River rise",
        "Answer":"Minnesota",
        "Options":"Texas,Minnesota,California,Indiana"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Name the capital city of the u.s",
        "Answer":"Washington D.C",
        "Options":"Texas,Arizona,Washington D.C,Indiana"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which Two states is Washington D.C located in",
        "Answer":"Maryland & Virginia",
        "Options":"Texas& Arizona,Maryland &Virginia,California& Indiana,NC & SC"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which is largest City in California",
        "Answer":"Los Angeles & L.A",
        "Options":"Los Angeles &L.A,Arizona& California,Indiana&Texes,Seattle&kent"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which is largest city in United States",
        "Answer":"New York",
        "Options":"New York,Arizona,California,Indiana"
    },
    {
        "Question":"In What state is the located in ;Chicago",
        "Answer":"Illinois",
        "Options":"Illinois,Chicago,California,Indiana"
    },
    {
        "Question":" In What state is this located in;Philadelphia",
        "Answer":"Philadelphia",
        "Options":"Arizona,California,Indiana,Philadelphia"
    },
    {
        "Question":"In what state is this located in;Detroit",
        "Answer":"Michigan",
        "Options":"Michigan,California,Indiana,Detroit"
    },
    {
        "Question":"In what state is the located in;Cincinnati",
        "Answer":"Ohio",
        "Options":"Texas,Ohio,California,Indiana"
    },
    {
        "Question":"In what state is this located in;St.Louis",
        "Answer":"Missouri",
        "Options":"Texas,Seattle,Missouri,Indiana"
    },
    {
        "Question":"In what state is this located in;Houston",
        "Answer":"Texas",
        "Options":"Texas,Arizona,California,Houston"
    },
    {
        "Question":"In what state is this located in;Seattle",
        "Answer":"Washington",
        "Options":"Washington,Arizona,seattle,Indiana"
    },
    {
        "Question":"In what state is this located in;Denver",
        "Answer":"Colorado",
        "Options":"Denver,Arizona,California,Colorado"
    },
    {
        "Question":"In what state is this located in ;Salt lake City",
        "Answer":"Utah",
        "Options":"Utah,Arizona,California,Indiana"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which ocean borders the U.S on the west?",
        "Answer":"Pacific",
        "Options":"Pacific,Arizona,California,Indiana"
    },
    
    {
        "Question":"Which is largest state in United States",
        "Answer":"Arizona",
        "Options":"Texas , Arizona, California, Indiana"
    },
    
{
    "Question":"Which is largest river in United States",
    "Answer":"Nile",
    "Options":"Texas , Nile, Missisippi, Indiana"
}
]


